[
	{
		"question": "A for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Apple"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "B for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Banana"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "C for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Cat","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Cat"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "D for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Dog"],
		"answer": ["Dog"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "E for ?",
		"choice": ["Elephant","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Elephant"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "F for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Fan","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Fan"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "G for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Gun","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Gun"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "H for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Hen","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Hen"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "I for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","India","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["India"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "J for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Jogging","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Jogging"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "K for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Kite","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Kite"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "L for ?",
		"choice": ["Light","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Light"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "M for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Mangao"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "N for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Night","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Night"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "O for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Orange"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "P for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Peacock","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Peacock"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "Q for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Ques","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Ques"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "R for ?",
		"choice": ["Rat","Orange","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Rat"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "S for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Ship","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Ship"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "T for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Time","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Time"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "U for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Umbrella","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Umbrella"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "V for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Vikas","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Vikas"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "W for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Window","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Apple"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "X for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","X-Men","Banana","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["X-Men"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "Y for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Yamaha","Mangao"],
		"answer": ["Yamaha"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	},
	{
		"question": "Z for ?",
		"choice": ["Apple","Orange","Banana","Zebra"],
		"answer": ["Apple"],
		"isMultipleChoice": false
	}
]